{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116861480","data":{"timestamp":" 948116861480"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 83461894-a193-43aa-9abb-4f0e4f8445d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116863610","data":{"timestamp":" 948116863609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 83461894-a193-43aa-9abb-4f0e4f8445d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116865164","data":{"timestamp":" 948116865164"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 83461894-a193-43aa-9abb-4f0e4f8445d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116866271","data":{"timestamp":" 948116866271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 83461894-a193-43aa-9abb-4f0e4f8445d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116866395","data":{"timestamp":" 948116866395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 83461894-a193-43aa-9abb-4f0e4f8445d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116888596","data":{"timestamp":" 948116888596"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116891565","data":{"timestamp":" 948116891565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116893127","data":{"timestamp":" 948116893127"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116896503","data":{"timestamp":" 948116896502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116898104","data":{"timestamp":" 948116898103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116904003","data":{"timestamp":" 948116904003"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116905567","data":{"timestamp":" 948116905566"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116910308","data":{"timestamp":" 948116910307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116911864","data":{"timestamp":" 948116911864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116915122","data":{"timestamp":" 948116915121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116916678","data":{"timestamp":" 948116916678"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116919813","data":{"timestamp":" 948116919813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116920765","data":{"timestamp":" 948116920764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116920841","data":{"timestamp":" 948116920841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" ca15505a-1896-4c4d-9cfd-26dc4256a949"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116954502","data":{"timestamp":" 948116954502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_11-7-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116961118","data":{"timestamp":" 948116961118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_11-7-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116966550","data":{"timestamp":" 948116966550"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116973138","data":{"timestamp":" 948116973138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116978876","data":{"timestamp":" 948116978876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-9-14"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116983397","data":{"timestamp":" 948116983397"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 17"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116989058","data":{"timestamp":" 948116989058"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116994038","data":{"timestamp":" 948116994038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117000296","data":{"timestamp":" 948117000296"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117005003","data":{"timestamp":" 948117005003"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_8-7-15"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117011173","data":{"timestamp":" 948117011173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_8-7-15"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117017282","data":{"timestamp":" 948117017282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117023520","data":{"timestamp":" 948117023520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117029410","data":{"timestamp":" 948117029410"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117033989","data":{"timestamp":" 948117033989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-4-14"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117038697","data":{"timestamp":" 948117038697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117045219","data":{"timestamp":" 948117045219"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117051823","data":{"timestamp":" 948117051822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117058974","data":{"timestamp":" 948117058973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" fc24100e-131a-4dc8-8ae1-19ebb6568e96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117068056","data":{"timestamp":" 948117068056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117069090","data":{"timestamp":" 948117069090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117072348","data":{"timestamp":" 948117072348"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117073379","data":{"timestamp":" 948117073379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117076090","data":{"timestamp":" 948117076090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117077124","data":{"timestamp":" 948117077124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117082081","data":{"timestamp":" 948117082081"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117083113","data":{"timestamp":" 948117083112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117089163","data":{"timestamp":" 948117089162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117090191","data":{"timestamp":" 948117090191"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117094835","data":{"timestamp":" 948117094835"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117095873","data":{"timestamp":" 948117095873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117104407","data":{"timestamp":" 948117104407"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117105472","data":{"timestamp":" 948117105472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117109449","data":{"timestamp":" 948117109449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117110478","data":{"timestamp":" 948117110478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117113655","data":{"timestamp":" 948117113655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117114695","data":{"timestamp":" 948117114695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117117816","data":{"timestamp":" 948117117816"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117118848","data":{"timestamp":" 948117118847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117125551","data":{"timestamp":" 948117125551"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117126622","data":{"timestamp":" 948117126622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117132154","data":{"timestamp":" 948117132154"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117133197","data":{"timestamp":" 948117133196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948117134541","data":{"timestamp":" 948117134541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_164726"," gameId":" 27416111-898d-4e1b-b3b9-ed844aaa3d62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}